(Sheldon:)That's no dream for a scientist.
(Penny:)-Okay, what's the big surprise?
-Just a minute.
(Leonard:)This tray contains clues...
(Leonard:)...as to what you and I are going
to be doing on Valentine's Day.
(Penny:)Oh, wow, okay. Let's see.
We've got milk chocolate,
Swiss cheese, fondue.
(Penny:)My lactose-intolerant boyfriend
is gonna eat all this...
...then I'm gonna climb on his back
and rocket to the moon?
(Howard(on the phone):)No.
(Leonard:)But it does involve air travel.
(Leonard:)Okay. Um....
(Leonard:)Let me slice this Swiss cheese
with my Swiss Army knife...
(Leonard:)...and then you can wash it down...
(Leonard:)...with a cup
of Swiss Miss instant cocoa.
(Penny:)Okay, I'm starting to think
"Swiss" is key here.